Hello friends my name is Pradeep how are
you all today I have brought a new topic for you about
which you should definitely think for
example we are talking about a car
if you do not have a car and
you are going out for a trip with
a relative or a friend or a
son with you then what happens is that
after driving for some distance
we do not feel anything in between brother I
drive a little and I also feel the same
and if it is good then we should definitely give the car there is no
problem but before giving the car
you have to ask him that brother do I have a
valid
driving license to drive the vehicle I am driving, be it a four wheeler, two wheeler or whatever it is or not then if he
says that you must have a license then you will
show that, I do
not have it so if any such person,
relative friend or anyone
says this to you then you should immediately refuse him no matter if
he gets angry or anything happens
you should not give the car in his hands
because you do not know the car you are driving in the
next 5  In a minute, in 10 minutes or
what is going to happen on your way,
I mean I have seen this here, if
you are watching it on the screen, then
you can see this car, two people were traveling in this car,
one had a
driving license and the other did
not have a driving license, so
after driving for some time, the guy who did
not have a license said, friend, let me drive the car, I will drive the car, the person
next to him is fine, so
after driving for a short distance, the guy loses
control and that jacket is, there was an
accident with the big tank, it was so dangerous,
in this situation, the guy died on the spot
and the person who had a license was
next to him, he backed out, what will happen now, the
car does not have valid insurance, the car is
one year old, there is no
problem with valid insurance, but there was a lot of
problem, the guy who was driving the car did not have a
license, so
in this situation, two losses occurred,
one, due to the death of the guy, the guy who was going to get the
claim, he did not get it and
secondly, the claim for the car also did not pass  What happened is,
brother, I am telling the truth. If you do
n't have a valid driving license,
you won't get a claim for your vehicle. If you say so, then
some people take out photographs and
videos, which go viral, and
it becomes easy for the insurance company to
identify which
side the driver was sitting on. So, what I am telling
you is that you should
put it in one place that under no
circumstances should
you give the car to someone who doesn't have a driving license, even if
he gets angry. He will get
angry for a while and will not talk to
you. But if you give him the
car and God forbid, I am telling you that there is a
probability that after some time, if the
car meets with an accident and something goes
wrong, then you will be in a big problem.
I mean, I am saying this with confidence.
If you don't want to get into such a problem, then you have to
follow the rules. Even if you have valid
insurance,
along with insurance, you must also have a valid driving license.
If this does not happen, then your claim will
not be accepted.  You will get a
change, the car overturns, some major
accident happens in which the driver dies,
he gets stuck there and
cannot be taken out, so our
media has become very strong in that situation, someone took that
picture, took that video, it
went viral, then it reaches the insurance company before you,
so you have to keep this in
mind friends, I am
telling you a very important thing,
so if you really like this video, then I am
saying again that you must share this video with your friends and
relatives,
if you like this video